<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>IntegrassBlog</title>
		<link>blog.integrass.com</link>
		<description>Integrass blog</description>
		<atom:link href="blog.integrass.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

		<item>
			<title>Save time and money by outsourcing</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/save-time-and-money-outsourcing</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/save-time-and-money-outsourcing</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 12:14:16 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Finding the right talent is always difficult, and it’s especially hard when you’re trying to juggle management and other key tasks. But when a project arises, you may find yourself in a pinch to find a qualified employee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is where outsourcing can save the day. According to this &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www2.deloitte.com/content/dam/Deloitte/nl/Documents/operations/deloitte-nl-s&amp;amp;o-global-outsourcing-survey.pdf&quot;&gt;Deloitte survey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, outsourcing is expected to grow in the coming years due to its numerous advantages. The survey explains that the top three reasons companies outsource is to cut costs, to allow themselves to focus on their core competencies and to solve capacity issues. We also believe that a top advantage is that you have access to a larger talent pool. Through outsourcing, you can hire people from anywhere in the world and have them work remotely via the cloud.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Though outsourcing can scare some business leaders off, at Across Borders, we use our expertise to make the process easy. Our recruiters are subject matter experts, so you know your candidate is coming from someone who understands the industry and your needs. We also have deep ties to top talent, and we’re able to scale quickly to fit demand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With our Smart Sourcing services, your company can focus on its core, lower costs and balance risk and opportunity. We offer a full range of flexible sourcing models to meet your needs, whether it is operating your entire IT department or a portion of it. Check out what outsourcing can do for you here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Why your business needs Big Data more than ever</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/why-your-business-needs-big-data-more-ever</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/why-your-business-needs-big-data-more-ever</guid>
			<pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 12:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Big Data has been around for &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/ciocentral/2013/01/15/big-data-get-ready-for-the-2013-big-bang/#58dc695c38c5&quot;&gt;more than five years now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Even then, it was rocking the C-suite, as Forbes puts it, as executives began exploring what Big Data could do for them and understanding why it was so important.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So why are we still talking about it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, Big Data is bigger than ever. People are using mobile apps and engaging in e-commerce more, creating a wealth of structured and unstructured data—and it’s essential that companies begin using that to their advantage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bigdata.cioreview.com/news/the-role-of-big-data-in-businesses-and-mobile-app-development-nid-25423-cid-15.html&quot;&gt;CIOReview&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, using Big Data can help companies customize fine-tune their approach to marketing. But more importantly, the article says, Big Data allows companies to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn from the past&lt;/strong&gt;. All businesses face tough external situations, but with careful analysis of Big Data, companies can have a better handle on why things happened and what to do to stay on the path to success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prepare for the future&lt;/strong&gt;. There will always be surprises when it comes to business, but thankfully, Big Data can help predict them so companies can start preparing now—not when they happen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Give users what they want&lt;/strong&gt;. Almost every business today is using online methods, and experts can take advantage of that, learning from Big Data to create products, particularly mobile apps, that work the way users want them to.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re not using Big Data, or you don’t think you’re using it to its full potential, this all might scare you a little. But at Across Borders Management Consulting Group, we are the experts these articles are talking about. We specialize in Big Data analytics, integration and application managed services, and we can help your harness them and use them to their full advantage so you can get ahead. Read more about our services here, or give us a call at 352-720-3135.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The top 3 mobile app trends for 2018</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/top-3-mobile-app-trends-2018</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/top-3-mobile-app-trends-2018</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 13:49:53 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Mobile applications are constantly evolving thanks to new technology and consumer demands. The number of apps and downloads continue to rise, making it easier for consumers to be entertained, informed and in touch with the brands they like. As of March 2017, there were a whopping 2.8 million apps available to Android users and 2.2 million apps available in Apple’s App Store, according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.statista.com/statistics/276623/number-of-apps-available-in-leading-app-stores/&quot;&gt;Statista.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With such phenomenal demand, there’s no doubt staying ahead of the trends with apps is important. Here are some of the biggest trends we see coming for the rest of 2018.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More uses of virtual reality&lt;/strong&gt;. In fact, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nbcolympics.com/news/experience-2018-winter-olympics-virtual-reality&quot;&gt;NBC Olympics&lt;/a&gt; is providing over 50 hours of live virtual reality coverage of the 2018 Olympic Winter Games from PyeongChang, South Korea, which can be accessed through their NBC Sports VR app. We expect other companies to develop VR material that consumers can access via their smartphone this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;An increase of on-the-go service apps&lt;/strong&gt;. We’ve already seen Uber and GrubHub make a huge impact on people nationwide, and apps like those will likely continue to disrupt the service industry because of their convenience and user-friendliness. We can see more apps like these coming out for cleaning services, dry-cleaning pickups, food delivery, taxi services and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A rise in mobile payment apps&lt;/strong&gt;. More consumers are using their phones to store all of their credit cards. Because of that, more apps like Google Wallet, PayPal, Venmo and PayAnywhere will likely be developed and downloaded this year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But the most important thing you need to stay on trend? A mobile app, of course. Need help? Across Borders can develop a user-friendly app to meet your consumer needs and give you an advantage over your competitors. Call us at 352-720-3135 or email us at info@abmcg.com to learn how we can customize an app for you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Increase in cyberattacks means more security is needed in healthcare field</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/increase-cyberattacks-means-more-security-needed-healthcare-field</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/increase-cyberattacks-means-more-security-needed-healthcare-field</guid>
			<pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 14:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Patient confidentiality is extremely important in the healthcare industry. Unfortunately, cyber-attackers threaten the ability to protect a patient’s information. Protecting private health-related information is an ongoing effort involving careful user practice and stronger software security.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-oxfordshire-39556062&quot;&gt;BBC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, in 2016, 55 National Health Service hospital trusts in England reported cyberattack problems. This is a sharp increase from 16 attacks from the year before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ransomware, a type of cyberattack, is part of the rise in attacks. Ransomware is software which locks computer systems, then demands a ransom for the data to be unlocked. As more information is being stored electronically, digital records are at greater risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With ransomware becoming more prevalent, it’s critical for companies to create backups of all data. By creating back-up files, a company holds the power instead of being held hostage. There’s no need to pay the cyber-attackers if the locked data can be accessed elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best solution to fighting off cyberattacks is to have a plan of action in place. Set up preventative measures, such as data encryption and employee training. Being proactive can help any company avoid falling victim to cyberattacks, but it is especially important in the sensitive healthcare field.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Across Borders Management Consulting Group has experience in the healthcare field, including with hospitals, pharmaceutical companies and research institutions. We are able to customize solutions to support infrastructure integration, member interactions, claims management and more—all while ensuring the tightest security. Reach out today to see what we can do for you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How much can cyberattacks really cost?</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/how-much-can-cyberattacks-really-cost</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/how-much-can-cyberattacks-really-cost</guid>
			<pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 14:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Sure, you’ve heard about cyberattacks. But if you’re with a small or mid-sized company, having your own cyberattack plan might seem like taking “better safe than sorry” a little too far. And if you’re a bigger company, it might not be the top priority — however, it may save you thousands, if not millions, of dollars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cyberattacks are on the rise, and it’s unlikely for the increase to stop anytime soon. With the high cost of data breaches, it’s definitely worth your while to invest in cybersecurity measures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.csoonline.com/article/3227065/security/cyber-attacks-cost-us-enterprises-13-million-on-average-in-2017.html&quot;&gt;to this article by CSO&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, the average cost of cyberattacks in 2017 on U.S. enterprises is $1.3 million and $117,000 for small and medium-sized businesses. That was part of an 11 percent increase globally. Cybersecurity needs to be looked at as a lifelong investment. With cyberattacks continuing to rise in America, your company is more at risk than ever before. Businesses of all sizes are expanding their IT budgets so they can ensure they won’t lose out on thousands of dollars if a cyberattack did occur.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The article lines up the incidents that had the most severe financial impact in 2017. The incident that cost enterprises the most money was physical loss of devices or media containing data at $2.8 million, followed closely by incidents affecting IT infrastructure hosted by a third party at $2.2 million. Interestingly, the incidents affecting small- to medium-sized businesses varied greatly from enterprises. Targeted attacks had the biggest financial impact at $188,000, with incidents involving non-computing connected devices coming in second at $152,000.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spend your IT security budget wisely. At Across Borders, we are experts at helping both small and large companies customize a plan to protect themselves. We offer security controls that deliver predictive analytics, prioritized threat data and real-time monitoring. Our services can help your company stay safe and save thousands. Contact us today to see how we can optimize a plan for your company and its needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Across Borders Management Consulting Group honored among top Central Florida technology companies</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/across-borders-management-consulting-group-honored-among-top-central-florida-technology-companies</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/across-borders-management-consulting-group-honored-among-top-central-florida-technology-companies</guid>
			<pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 14:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Orlando Business Journal selects firm for Innovations in Technology Awards&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MOUNT DORA, Fla. (Nov. 8, 2017) – Across Borders Management Consulting Group recently received the Orlando Business Journal’s Innovations in Technology Award for its outstanding contributions to the industry in Central Florida.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The awards honor both individuals and companies that embrace technology to positively impact both the top and bottom lines. They are open to small, medium and large companies, as well as to nonprofits, government and research organizations and those in education, health care and tourism. Companies must have a physical location in Orange, Osceola, Seminole, Lake, Brevard or Volusia counties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Across Borders was among 17 businesses and two individuals to receive the award.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“At Across Borders, we’re all about technology,” said Managing Partner Arathi Rajagopalan. “But we aren’t just looking for the next big thing. We think about the ways technology can help people and businesses move forward and reach their goals. That’s what these awards are all about, and we’re honored to be recognized by OBJ.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Across Borders is a technology solutions provider that implements customized, end-to-end IT solutions to help businesses expand and become user-friendly. Across Borders has delivered quality consulting solutions to many clients, including Fortune 500 companies such as Microsoft, Walgreens, Citibank and Toyota.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The company is woman and minority owned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Across Borders has been growing and expanding rapidly. In 2017, the company was named to the Inc. 5000 for the third time in a row. It was also named to OBJ’s list of the 50 fastest growing companies for the second year in a row. Additionally, the company recently entered the South Florida and Atlanta markets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information on Across Borders Management Consulting Group LLC Dba Integrass, visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.integrass.com&quot;&gt;www.integrass.com.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About Across Borders Management Consulting Group Across Borders Management Consulting Group is a global technology solutions provider that offers clients both customized, end-to-end IT solutions and products that are ready to launch through its product division, Fobess. Across Borders has expertise in the finance, health care and retail fields. Its products make it easy to launch everything from food delivery businesses and custom T-shirt design to job websites. The company, which began operations in 2011, is woman and minority owned and based in Mount Dora, Fla. Across Borders has been honored numerous times for its outstanding growth. It has been named to the Inc. 5000 list three times and made the Orlando Business Journal’s Fast 50 in 2016 and 2017. It has also been named among Florida Companies to Watch by GrowFL. For more information, call (352) 720-3135 or visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.integrass.com&quot;&gt;www.integrass.com.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How the cloud can increase company collaboration</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/how-cloud-can-increase-company-collaboration</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/how-cloud-can-increase-company-collaboration</guid>
			<pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 14:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Working on the cloud offers numerous advantages to business of all sizes, from disaster recovery to automatic software updates. The most important advantage, however, may be increased collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s nothing harder than working on a single file located on the server. Only one person can access the file at a time and real-time updates are hard to implement. If two people are trying to add ideas to a project, the number of files grows exponentially and will later need to be merged, which can be a real time-killer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Working on the cloud changes all of that. Team members can access, edit and share documents anytime from anywhere. With real-time updates and full visibility on their contributions, workers have the ability to collaborate more effectively and efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://whattheythink.com/articles/87907-collaboration-low-hanging-fruit-cloud-migration/&quot;&gt;What They Think&lt;/a&gt; provides a great real-world example of how working on the cloud both increases collaboration and saves time. On Fridays, the owner of a company would send out an Excel document to 25 employees and ask them to fill in their personal updates. The owner would receive 25 documents back and would combine them all into a single master. Once the owner switched to the cloud, one single link was sent to all 25 employees and the employees could then enter their data in real time. With one file to work with, there was better visibility of the project, and the owner was able to spend his time on more productive tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If your company is looking to streamline processes in 2018, cloud migration has to be part of your plan. Across Borders’ Cloud Migration Advisory will help your company utilize the cloud to the max. We’ll analyze your applications and evaluate how each will scale within the cloud. From analyzing who uses the application, how much memory and storage it’ll need, licensing restrictions and security considerations, we’ll identify target applications and application dependency maps to see which applications can be migrated first. Put simply, we’ll find the right solution to fit your company. Click here to read more on how our services can help you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Keeping healthcare information safe as the demand for technology grows</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/keeping-healthcare-information-safe-demand-technology-grows</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/keeping-healthcare-information-safe-demand-technology-grows</guid>
			<pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 13:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;When you walk into your doctor’s office or a hospital and the care giver asks for your personal information, you don’t hesitate. You know they need that information to give you the best treatment options, and your health is the most important thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, as cyberattacks against the healthcare industry continue to grow, you might start to think twice about the security of your health information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://http://www.idtheftcenter.org/images/breach/2017Breaches/ITRCBreachStatsReportSummary2017.pdf&quot;&gt;Identity Theft Resource Center,&lt;/a&gt; medical or healthcare breaches made up 28 percent of all data breaches in 2017—second only to breaches in the business category.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2016, the College of Healthcare Information Management Executives administered a survey of more than 100 CIOs. The survey found that 81 percent of the respondents said strengthening data security was a top goal, even ahead of increasing patient satisfaction and physician satisfaction. The survey also revealed that 68 percent of respondents said the implementing a secure text messaging solution is an active project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The figures reveal that today’s treatment plans require coordination of care teams quickly and effectively—and that requires technology. But without the proper precautions, information can be at the fingertips of hackers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Across Borders has been closely following these changes in the healthcare industry. In fact, the healthcare industry is one of our core competencies. We can help hospitals and other healthcare institutions implement technology solutions that streamline business processes and improve patient/physician experiences—all in a way that keeps important information safe.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How technology could change the banking industry in 2018</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/how-technology-could-change-banking-industry-2018</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/how-technology-could-change-banking-industry-2018</guid>
			<pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 13:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;In the past, there was no choice but to take your paycheck to the bank, wait in line, and make a deposit. These days, there are electronic deposits, payments via Paypal or Venmo and even advances like Bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Banks must be updating constantly to keep up with consumer trends or risk being left behind—and that’s not going to change any time soon. In fact, members of the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesfinancecouncil/2017/03/06/seven-big-changes-coming-to-the-banking-industry/#3a34c2d03402&quot;&gt;Forbes Finance Council&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; said there could be some huge industry changes in the next year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to one of the members, paper checks won’t be used anymore. Risk of fraud and identity theft is high with paper checks, and advances like chip cards are more secure and more common.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another predicted trend is that people will continue to change the way they pay. Few people actually go into a bank to withdraw money to pay in cash. Now, if someone owes money, they’ll use an application like Paypal or Venmo to make a transfer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin has been making a name for itself this past year, and it’s not going away, according to the article. Digital currency will continue to grow as we move toward a cashless society.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Banks are also predicted to partner with fintech companies to meet consumer need, become more consumer-friendly and compete.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What does that all mean for you? The underlying theme of all of these expert predictions is technology. Those in the banking and financial service industry need to embrace technology to stay ahead of industry changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Luckily, the industry is one of Across Borders’ core competencies. We can help you find the system you need to drive value for your customers and become a market leader. Read more about our banking and financial industry solutions here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Keeping up with the consumer</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/keeping-consumer</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/keeping-consumer</guid>
			<pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;We’ve all heard the phrase “keeping up with the times.” However, as a company, it’s more important to keep up with consumer. They’re always on the go, and you should be too—or risk missing out on business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With increasing usage of laptops, tablets and cell phones for pleasure and on-the-go work, it’s vital your website and mobile applications are user-friendly and work smoothly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having a mobile application developed and ensuring your website is reactive is the first step in increasing engagement with consumers. What many companies don’t realize, however, is that you can’t stop there. According to &lt;a href=&quot;https://searchitoperations.techtarget.com/tip/Continuous-delivery-DevOps-and-cloud-vital-pieces-of-modernization&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TechTarget&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, applications need to be modernized continuously. Application modernization projects, however, can often become caught up in technical issues and disconnected from the real goals of the project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TechTarget’s article focuses on how project goals should drive the methods used in application modernization—and we completely agree. Too often, companies put the cart before the horse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Across Borders, we specialize in looking at your existing platforms and applications before making a plan so we can both drive business and customize a solution that fits seamlessly with your system. And of course, we are experts in the most innovative technology solutions for all of your mobility needs, including mobile websites, enterprise mobility solutions, mobile applications and mobile porting solutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get on the right track to keep up with your consumers. Call us at 352-720-3164 to get started.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Are you ready for the holiday shoppers?</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/are-you-ready-holiday-shoppers</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/are-you-ready-holiday-shoppers</guid>
			<pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 10:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Holidays are celebrated in many different ways, but there’s usually one constant—presents. Whether you celebrate Christmas, Hanukkah, Kwanzaa or just the overall season, December is a prime month to boost sales. And traditional, in-store shopping is no longer the only way to capitalize on that demand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/holiday-spending-american-consumers-2017-11&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Business Insider&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Americans are planning to spend about $862 on gifts this season, which is a big increase from the $752 Americans said they planned on spending last season. &lt;a href=&quot;https://americanresearchgroup.com/holiday/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;American Research Group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; also found that the 61% of American adults surveyed plan to use the internet to purchase gifts, which is an all-time high.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It may be too late to implement an improved system for your business this year, but the trend is pretty clear, and it’s not going to change any time soon. To match this demand, you need to offer your customers a stress-free experience. This may mean some updates to both your websites and mobile applications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People avoid in-person shopping to skip lines and escape the claustrophobic stores. But with the influx of online shoppers, your website may slow down. To offer the most pleasant experience, you must ensure your website is powerful enough to handle the influx of shoppers quickly, reliably, and efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mobile applications can also be a pain for shopping if they aren’t updated and optimized for functionality, such as if there isn’t a detailed navigation bar and search option.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re watching others’ sales outpace yours, now is the time to start preparing for next season’s holiday shopping rush. At Across Borders, we can not only make sure your website and app are functioning at top levels, we can also create an experience that engages customers across platforms, collects critical insights, and meets essential regulatory requirements. Call us at 407-641-9560 to start your update today.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Across Borders Management Consulting Group ranked in top 100 fastest growing companies in Florida</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/across-borders-management-consulting-group-ranked-top-100-fastest-growing-companies-florida</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/across-borders-management-consulting-group-ranked-top-100-fastest-growing-companies-florida</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 13:22:26 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Across Borders Management Consulting Group is extremely excited and honored to be ranked in The Business Journals&#039; highly prestigious Florida Fast 100 list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Companies were ranked based on the percentage change in gross revenue from 2014 to 2016. The list included companies from the entire state of Florida. Across Borders showed an astounding 75.57% change in gross revenue since 2014.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The recognition is the latest in a series of honors for Across Borders. The company was also ranked in OBJ&#039;s Central Florida&#039;s Largest Women-Owned Businesses list, Inc. 5000&#039;s Fastest Growing Private Companies in America 2017 list and was named to OBJ&#039;s Fast 50 list this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To see the full Florida Fast 100 list, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bizjournals.com/orlando/subscriber-only/2017/09/15/florida-fast-100.html&quot;&gt;click here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Better Business Process Management can mean a more flexible, efficient company</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/better-business-process-management-can-mean-more-flexible-efficient-company</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/better-business-process-management-can-mean-more-flexible-efficient-company</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 13:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Companies are created with big goals in mind, and business processes are established with the company’s development. However, these processes become stagnant if overlooked, and the company will follow suit. To help your business continue to evolve, your BPM needs to be continually refreshed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BPM is the key to the way your company operates. These processes are followed for every business function and allow all company departments to work together and interact with customers. It’s a direct reflection on how flexible your company is, so it’s time to take a hard look at your processes and how they can be updated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some companies claim their business processes are just the way things have always been done or they create their BPM in a management setting without seeing how it actually plays out in everyday tasks. These development methods hamper how a company operates and ultimately decrease efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BPM needs to be thought of as a continuous practice rather than a one-time set up, as businesses are ever-changing. If a company’s business processes are analyzed continually, a company can see what processes are working and what needs to be improved upon. A monitored BPM is flexible, leading to a company’s flexibility as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not too late to jump start your business processes. Across Borders Management Consulting Group’s BPM solutions are designed to transform rigid IT environments and align processes with business objectives. Contact Across Borders today to set up a plan to help you adapt to and anticipate shifts in your market.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The high cost of not having a Project Management Office</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/high-cost-not-having-project-management-office</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/high-cost-not-having-project-management-office</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 12:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Starting a project can seem like a daunting task, especially when the odds are stacked against you. That’s where a Project Management Office comes into play. With this project management system, direction, scheduling, budgeting and associated risks are accounted for. PMO is there from the establishment of a project, to the measurement and risk assessment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CIO explains &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cio.com/article/2427972/project-management/article.html&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;in this article&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that poor project performance can cause organizations to waste $97 million for every $1 billion invested in projects. It’s clear that having a project management system is a worthwhile investment, as it can save your company millions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CIO’s article also lays out seven keys steps to delivering better projects. It includes aligning company goals with project management, bridging the gap between strategy and execution, and adopting the right technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Across Borders, we agree with all of these points—and we can help you achieve them. With our PMO, we set up the implementation to fit your business’s goals. We also support the basics, like project prioritization and risk management, so you can get things done. And to say we will help you adopt the right technology is an understatement. We know the industry inside and out, and we will help you select the right tools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Align your project goals and prioritize your business’ needs with PMO. See more on our PMO services here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After all, can your business afford to be on the wrong side of poor project performance?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Across Borders ranked in OBJ&#039;s Largest Minority-Owned Businesses list</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/across-borders-ranked-objs-largest-minority-owned-businesses-list</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/across-borders-ranked-objs-largest-minority-owned-businesses-list</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 13:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Across Borders Management Consulting Group is honored to be No. 16 in Orlando Business Journal&#039;s list of Largest Minority-Owned Businesses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Companies were ranked based on their 2016 Central Florida revenue. The list included companies from Lake, Orange, Osceola and Seminole counties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The recognition is the latest in a series of honors for Across Borders. The company was also ranked in The Business Journals&#039; Florida Fast 100 list, OBJ&#039;s Central Florida&#039;s Largest Women-Owned Businesses list, Inc. 5000&#039;s Fastest Growing Private Companies in America 2017 list and was named to OBJ&#039;s Fast 50 list this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To see the full OBJ Largest Minority-Owned Businesses list, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bizjournals.com/orlando/subscriber-only/2017/10/06/largest-minority-owned-businesses-in.html&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Move faster, save money—staff augmentation is the solution</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/move-faster-save-moneystaff-augmentation-solution</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/move-faster-save-moneystaff-augmentation-solution</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 13:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Finding skilled manpower for a short-term project can prove a daunting task. It may seem next to impossible to find a candidate with experience who fits your team and is flexible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is where staff augmentation comes into play. With this business solution, you can focus on the growth and development of your business, while giving you the access you need to experienced professionals when you need them. This lowers unnecessary overhead costs and it ensures you’re meeting your goals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are some additional benefits to staff augmentation:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flexibility&lt;/strong&gt;. Having the ability to adapt to the industry can help your company stay ahead of competitors. With staff augmentation, you can put in more manpower on work when needed, and cut back when times are slow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Less risk&lt;/strong&gt;. Staff augmentation allows you to keep your projects in-house, while adding knowledgeable professionals to bring the skills needed to succeed. When fully outsourcing a project, it’s harder to keep an eye on things and make sure work is going in the direction you want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost effective&lt;/strong&gt;. You’re only paying for the work you need when you need it. Staff augmentation ensures you won’t have unnecessary full-time employees.
Why Across Borders staff augmentation? Our recruiters understand the industry, they have decades of experience working with candidates, and we have relationships with top talent. If you think staff augmentation is the right solution for your business needs, contact Across Borders Management Consulting Group today. We’ll efficiently optimize staffing and present the best professionals in the industry. Read more about what sets Across Borders’ recruiting and staff augmentation apart here.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Across Borders expands to two new markets</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/across-borders-expands-two-new-markets</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/across-borders-expands-two-new-markets</guid>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 13:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Technology solutions firm will offer services in South Florida, Atlanta areas&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MOUNT DORA, Fla. (Aug. 31, 2017)&lt;/strong&gt; – Across Borders Management Consulting Group LLC Dba Integrass, a thriving technology solutions provider, is expanding to two new markets across the Southeast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The company, which is based in Central Florida, will enter the South Florida market with an office in Fort Lauderdale. Across Borders is also planning to enter the Atlanta market, and the company is actively recruiting top candidates for that office.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The expansion comes after a period of significant growth. The company has been named to the Inc. 5000 list three times, a feat accomplished by only a small fraction of the tens of thousands of applicants over the years. It has also been named among the Florida Companies to Watch by GrowFL and, earlier this year, to the Orlando Business Journal’s list of the 50 fastest growing companies for the second year in a row, growing revenues by more than 75 percent over the last three years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Across Borders implements customized, end-to-end IT solutions using open source and industry standard proprietary platforms, as well as offering easy to deploy software and tools to help businesses hit the ground running and promote growth. The company has extensive experience and expertise in the finance, health care and retail fields.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information about Across Borders, visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.integrass.com&quot;&gt;www.integrass.com.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Across Borders Management Consulting Group LLC Dba Integrass&lt;/strong&gt; is a global technology solutions provider that offers clients both customized, end-to-end IT solutions and products that are ready to launch through its product division, Fobess. Across Borders has expertise in the finance, health care and retail fields. Its products make it easy to launch everything from food delivery businesses and custom T-shirt design to job websites. The company, which began operations in 2011, is woman and minority owned and based in Mount Dora, Fla. Across Borders has been honored numerous times for its outstanding growth. It has been named to the Inc. 5000 list three times and made the Orlando Business Journal’s Fast 50 in 2016 and 2017. It has also been named among Florida Companies to Watch by GrowFL. For more information, call (352) 720-3135 or visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.integrass.com&quot;&gt;www.integrass.com.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Across Borders ranked in OBJ&#039;s list of Central Florida&#039;s Largest Women-Owned Businesses</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/across-borders-ranked-objs-list-central-floridas-largest-women-owned-businesses</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/across-borders-ranked-objs-list-central-floridas-largest-women-owned-businesses</guid>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 13:23:38 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Across Borders Management Consulting Group is honored to be No. 18 in Orlando Business Journal&#039;s list of Central Florida&#039;s Largest Women-Owned Businesses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Companies were ranked based on their 2016 Central Florida gross revenue. The list included companies from Lake, Orange, Osceola and Seminole counties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The recognition is the latest in a series of honors for Across Borders. The company was also ranked in Inc. 5000&#039;s Fastest Growing Private Companies in America 2017 list and was named to OBJ&#039;s Fast 50 list this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To see the full OBJ Central Florida&#039;s Largest Women-Owned Businesses list, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bizjournals.com/orlando/subscriber-only/2017/09/15/c-flas-largest-women-owned-businesses.html&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How Big Data means big results for nonprofits</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/how-big-data-means-big-results-nonprofits</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/how-big-data-means-big-results-nonprofits</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 14:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Dealing with limited resources is a challenge almost every nonprofit faces. Whether it is figuring out a way to communicate with clients and volunteers, tracking important statistics or keeping financials in line, it seems like every organization is trying to do more with less.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But though it might seem like cutting-edge technology is out of reach for nonprofits on a budget, it doesn’t have to be—and it can make a huge difference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Across Borders has experience helping nonprofits communicate via e-newsletters, acquire volunteers electronically and provide online ways to donate and track costs. We also have experience with Big Data, another area that can mean big results for nonprofits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One way Big Data can make a difference is in fundraising. A nonprofit may be spreading itself thin putting resources into emails, direct mail, and fundraising events. Big Data can help nonprofits look at its supporters and see which fundraising effort generated the most response. On top of that, it can predict future trends and help nonprofits make informed decisions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big Data can also help nonprofits in their missions. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/3068036/how-big-data-could-find-simpler-cheaper-ways-to-repair-wildlife-ecosystems&quot;&gt;A perfect example is Freshwater Trust,&lt;/a&gt; a nonprofit working on river conservation. This nonprofit utilized Big Data to find the best solution to preserving a river in Oregon. Information about environmental factors, such as vegetation, amount of sunlight and slope of land, were gathered to create maps for water restoration projects. The maps were color coded based on priority, where the highest priority areas would have the most impact at the lowest cost. By utilizing this information, Freshwater Trust saved millions of dollars and provided new employment opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The amount of information Big Data provides is invaluable. Across Borders Management Consulting Group is here to help you make the most of the information. We strive to help nonprofits make the most of their missions—because giving back is part of our mission. Read more about our work in the nonprofit sector here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Across Borders Management Consulting Group named to Inc. 5000 for third year</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/across-borders-management-consulting-group-named-inc-5000-third-year</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/across-borders-management-consulting-group-named-inc-5000-third-year</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 13:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Technology solutions firm ranks among fastest growing companies in U.S.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MOUNT DORA, Fla. (Aug. 17, 2017) – Across Borders Management Consulting Group has been named among the fastest growing private companies in the U.S. for the third year in a row.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The company was ranked on the annual Inc. 5000 list, which features the most elite among nearly seven million private companies. Across Borders’ repeated success puts it among even more rarefied company, as it has made consistent and notable gains for three years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“For us to receive this incredible recognition not only once, but three times, is a testament to the work Across Borders does for our customers,” said Managing Partner Arathi Rajagopalan. “We’re honored and look forward to continuing this phenomenal growth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Across Borders was ranked No. 3,825 on the list, coming in with 2016 revenue of $4 million and 77 percent growth over three years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Based in Mount Dora, Across Borders has 40 employees and is a minority and woman-owned business. The company is a global technology solutions provider offering both customized, end-to-end IT solutions and easy to deploy software and tools to help businesses grow. Areas of expertise include finance, health care and retail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information, visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.integrass.com&quot;&gt;www.integrass.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About Across Borders Management Consulting Group Across Borders Management Consulting Group is a global technology solutions provider that offers clients both customized, end-to-end IT solutions and products that are ready to launch through its product division, Fobess. Across Borders has expertise in the finance, health care and retail fields. Its products make it easy to launch everything from food delivery businesses and custom T-shirt design to job websites. The company, which began operations in 2011, is woman and minority owned and based in Mount Dora, Fla. Across Borders has been honored numerous times for its outstanding growth. It has been named to the Inc. 5000 list three times and made the Orlando Business Journal’s Fast 50 in 2016 and 2017. It has also been named among Florida Companies to Watch by GrowFL. For more information, call (352) 720-3135 or visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.integrass.com&quot;&gt;www.integrass.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Big Data can save your life</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/big-data-can-save-your-life</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/big-data-can-save-your-life</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 14:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Learning how to use Big Data to its fullest potential is a real game changer. From deepening customer relations to predicting future trends, your business can stand out in its industry. Big Data can change the world, and its impact is already showing. Thanks to the information being collected on patients, the healthcare industry is becoming much more advanced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the healthcare industry, Big Data can improve the quality of life and decrease the number of deaths. Patients divulge more information now than ever before thanks to modern technology. With mobile applications and wearable technology, such as Fitbits and Apple Watches, doctors can analyze their patient’s workout patterns, food and water intake, and heart rate. Ultimately, this will allow doctors to prevent medical issues, such as heart attacks, as they can detect early warning signs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personalized medicine is making big strides in the healthcare industry. With this practice, doctors integrate people’s genetic blueprint and lifestyle data and create a customized treatment plan. Each patient’s information can be compared to thousands of others, helping to detect patterns. This allows doctors to predict a patient’s illness and determine the best possible treatment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Across Border Management Consulting Group, we’ll provide the insights you need to make better business decisions. Text and predictive analytics, data mining, reporting and planning are a few of our specialties, which will help your organization thrive. To read more on information management and Big Data, visit our website here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Why cloud deployment is becoming key for businesses</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/why-cloud-deployment-becoming-key-businesses</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/why-cloud-deployment-becoming-key-businesses</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 14:06:20 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;The cloud is no longer a new technology, and the benefits of cloud deployment are amazing. Major organizations such as Coca Cola, HTC, Best Buy and General Mills are taking advantage of cloud technology. Whether you’re looking for flexibility, increased collaboration, automatic software updates or quick disaster recovery, the cloud can make sure your system is reliable and stress-free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Netflix and Airbnb are both pioneers in cloud-based services. With a vast selection of movies and television shows, Netflix users are now able to watch whatever they want, whenever they want. Airbnb’s services allow homeowners to rent their home out to vacationers, all with a click of their mouse. These cloud pioneers show how the cloud can deliver the convenience and savings people are searching for from home, the airport or even the beach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The fact that consumers are starting to expect the convenience and service offerings of the cloud means companies of all sizes need to get on board before they are left behind. Across Borders Management Consulting Group makes it easy. Working with the cloud is among our core offerings. We can help you determine what infrastructure is right for your needs, get you set up, and keep you on track. With the cloud, your security, accessibility, tracking, recovery, maintenance and more will be streamlined and simple—and your mind will be at ease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To learn more about our cloud deployment services, click here or give us a call today.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Drive new business value with application modernization</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/drive-new-business-value-application-modernization</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/drive-new-business-value-application-modernization</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 12:06:53 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;With rapidly changing technology, it’s time to keep up with the trends, such as modernizing applications to fit user needs. Some apps need to be re-platformed for various mediums, such as tablets, smartphones and computers. Programming languages also have changed, so slight tweaks to the structures are needed. Plus, users will LOVE the speed that comes along with these changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Creating new business value from your current applications is the ultimate goal of application modernization. Outdated software can prevent apps from performing the specific functions they were designed to do. There are various ways to modernize applications, such as rewriting the existing COBOL code to a more web-friendly programming language, or adding a web interface to keep portions of the existing application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To strategically advance in your industry, investing in maintenance and modernization is a must. However, also take into consideration the time and money that goes along with it. Timing is important to make the most of your money. Only start the modernization process once your current applications are going out of style.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Across Borders Management Consulting Group, we specialize in driving value from your existing platforms. We’ll customize your apps to your customer needs and implement innovative solutions. Learn more of our services &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.abmcg.com/solutions/application-migration-modernization&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; and contact us today to see how we can service you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How does Information Management Differ from Data Management?</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/how-does-information-management-differ-data-management</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/how-does-information-management-differ-data-management</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 14:10:20 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;As IT consultants we see this all the time….There is generally some confusion on what is needed to solve the problem in an organization’s IT infrastructure. We often ask clients what they are looking to improve or where they have a weakness. Some describe their problems with architecture and technology enablement, content delivery, business intelligence and performance management, enterprise data management or information asset management. Though the phrase “enterprise data management” seems like seems like it would be a data management problem, this one is really an information management problem. It is these instances where organizations miss the opportunity to correct the true problem. This happens regularly where IT directors and other industry professionals don’t classify the problem accurately. They implement a wrong solution then over time results show there are faults within the system. Time and money has been spent fixing a problem with a solution that does not fit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What makes Across Borders Consulting Group different from other IT consulting firms is we take the time to correctly diagnose the real problem and accurately create the right solution. There are significant differences between information management and data management.
According to Wikipedia information management is “the acquisition of information from one or more sources, the custodianship and the distribution of that information to those who need it and its ultimate disposition through archiving or deletion.” There are a variety of job functions associated with information management including those who need it for making decisions and people who are responsible for data safety, storage and disposal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Data management refers to the development and execution of data architectures, policies, practices and procedures that accurately maintain the data needs of an enterprise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We often see the breakdown in an IT infrastructure is not the data storage systems in place and security of the data, but rather the delivery and usage of the data for business intelligence purposes. It’s very typical for an organization to have the data available and nobody knows how to distribute the information internally. What’s even a bigger problem is reading the data and how to interpret. Data is useless without the skills to analyze it. Many people can access the data by generating reports and exporting the data. Where there is a breakdown is in the understanding of what the data means and how to draw conclusions or make recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Understanding the data and distributing the information would fall under the information management category which is far different than a data management problem. We strongly encourage IT professionals in all organizations to dig deep into their organization and take a look at where the inefficiencies may be occurring. Is it in the gathering and distribution of data (information management) or is it in the procedures for maintaining the data (data management?)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Generally, if there are concerns or issues with regard to data governance, data quality, master data management, data architecture, privacy/security or data retention and archiving you would be dealing with a data management issue(s). If the problems are more related to enterprise content management, enterprise data management, business intelligence, performance management, enterprise data management or content delivery you would be considering an information management approach to solving the problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Across Borders Management Consulting our team works with IT professionals in a variety of organizations. We offer project based coaching where we guide IT professionals in the implementation of solution(s). We also offer more long term consulting where we act as the IT department for our clients. In this scenario the daily, weekly and monthly IT tasks are outsourced to us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We offer the best IT management in the industry, customized solutions at competitive prices. For more information on how Across Borders Management Consulting Group can help your organization we invite you to contact our Mt. Dora, Florida office at 352-720-3135 or visit our contact page on our website located at: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.abmcg.com/company/contacts&quot;&gt;http://www.abmcg.com/company/contacts&lt;/a&gt; and describe your IT environment and how we can help you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Big data: What it is and how it’s impacting the healthcare industry</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/big-data-what-it-and-how-its-impacting-healthcare-industry</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/big-data-what-it-and-how-its-impacting-healthcare-industry</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 14:07:55 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Big data—you’ve heard the term throughout the years, yet you may not know what it is or how it affects you. With the potential to change the operation of multiple industries, including healthcare, big data shouldn’t be overlooked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big data is every bit of data a business or medical center gathers. In the healthcare industry, this includes appointment information, patient demographics, diagnoses, prescriptions and everything in between. As your medical practice goes through its daily routine, the information gathered is stored on a computer system. This stored data is then put through different algorithms that find patterns and predict future trends and changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it comes to clinical trials, patients are usually chosen from their applications. Big data provides predictive analytics, which makes it easier to find the perfect individuals for the trials. It can also help determine drug risks and environmental concerns. According to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.surgimedics.com/Research%20Articles/Electrosurgical%20Plume/Reducing%20The%20Danger%20Of%20Surgical%20Smoke%20Exposure%20To%20Health%20Care%20Workers.pdf&quot;&gt;Environment of Care News,&lt;/a&gt; many workers in the healthcare industry are exposed to laser and electro surgery smoke, which cause health problems for the employees. The use of big data has helped predict which procedures will cause laser smoke and what techniques will limit employee exposure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personalizing care is difficult because of the large number of patients medical practitioners see. Each patient has unique needs and prescribing drugs may be tricky. Some drugs may not work for certain individuals, causing doctors to go through a trial-and-error process. Big data can show a patient’s genetic profile, which will make it easier to prescribe a medicine that works.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Across Borders Management Consulting Group, we specialize in the healthcare industry and offer big data analytics. We’re here to help you make better business decisions and show the potential to grow. To learn more about our services, click here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Share the Love This Valentine’s Season!</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/share-love-valentines-season</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/share-love-valentines-season</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 14:02:34 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;How much do you love your employees? Have you realized the heart of your business is in your employees? It’s these people that make your business a success…or a failure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Human resource trends for 2017 suggest that investing in employees can help keep a company at the top of their game. With the influx of Millennials entering the workplace, emergent technologies, and focus on retaining current employees, a human resource department has its hands full. This is where an open source development company such as Fobess can help. Our consultants can help your company manage and streamline data. Transitioning from an antiquated system to a human resources management open source software can help improve work flow, streamline business processes, and eliminate redundancies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Collecting and using big data can help companies pinpoint areas that need improvement, help track employee development, and improve employee performance. Offering “perks” such as fitness memberships and in house massages is slowly going away in favor of offering employees flexible/remote work schedules and more opportunities to pursue professional goals such as continuing education.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The use of people analytics becomes more predictive. This technology helps companies identify the best candidates for a job, helps a company to re-organize structure, and can help retain employees by identifying key aspects of dissatisfaction. Every company and situation is different. Fobess offers customized, sophisticated human resources management technology to fit a company’s specific needs. Be it creating a tracking program that focuses on employee engagement, an analytical program to help with the hiring process, a program to provide employees with an ongoing performance review process, or even a mobile app so that future employees can apply for a job via their smart phone. The scope of human resource management software has improved over the years to also offer the ability for employees to access specific benefits such as vacation time accrual.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Streamlining human resource systems and generating real-time data is our goal for all HR software solutions we offer. Our open source human resource software applications are customizable and affordable for small to medium size businesses. If your business is struggling to manage employee records, benefits, sick time and leave it may be time to consider making a change to how you manage your human resources. We invite you to contact our Mt. Dora, Florida office at 352-720-3164 for a consultation. Let us help clean up your human resources functions so you can keep the employees you really LOVE!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Keeping up with e-commerce</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/keeping-e-commerce</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/keeping-e-commerce</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 14:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;E-commerce is rapidly growing and companies are struggling to keep up with this trend. Amazon is known for its quick e-commerce and companies are competing for customers to purchase from their online stores.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wal-Mart recently made improvements to its own e-commerce operations. In this effort, the giant retailer purchased ShoeBuy, Moosejaw and ModCloth since they have an online presence and large millennial reach. According to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/walmart-ramps-up-e-commerce-with-two-new-initiatives-2017-3&quot;&gt;Business Insider,&lt;/a&gt; Amazon dominates apparel online sales and these purchases allow Wal-Mart to compete.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wal-Mart’s drive for greater e-commerce sales is evidence of the growing operation. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.emarketer.com/Article/Worldwide-Retail-Ecommerce-Sales-Will-Reach-1915-Trillion-This-Year/1014369&quot;&gt;eMarketer&lt;/a&gt; explains that sales reached $1.915 trillion in 2016 and are expected to increase to $4.058 trillion in 2020. Setting up an easily accessible e-commerce website is vital to future success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Across Borders Management Consulting Group, we’re here to help your company’s e-commerce operations grow. Our solutions offer product browsing, catalog management, banking and financial services, customer service, search engine optimization and much more. From these, you’ll be open source and have an easy to manage software, a low-cost IT infrastructure, and integration with transaction gateways and CMS techniques.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’ll make your e-commerce operations easy to manage and help provide results. To learn more about our e-commerce solutions and benefits, click here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Add value to your brand and contribute to company growth with customized mobile apps</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/add-value-your-brand-and-contribute-company-growth-customized-mobile-apps</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/add-value-your-brand-and-contribute-company-growth-customized-mobile-apps</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 13:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Today, people seem to always be on the go and looking for the latest technology. People demand quick answers, easy access and time-saving applications. With society being reliant on technology, it’s important for businesses to offer what consumers are looking for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mobile applications may be the answer to growing your company. According to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2017/01/12/evolution-of-technology/&quot;&gt;Pew Research Center&lt;/a&gt;, 77 percent of all U.S. adults own a smartphone, compared with the 35 percent of adults with a smartphone in 2011. This dramatic increase shows that more people are turning to technology to stay connected with society and try to make their lives easier. The Apple App Store and Google Play, the Android app store, have over two million apps each, according to the statistics gathered by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.statista.com/statistics/276623/number-of-apps-available-in-leading-app-stores/&quot;&gt;Statista.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mobile applications can boost productivity and efficiency, give your company a competitive edge, and enhance user experience. When it comes to mobile applications, the user always comes first. Although aesthetic-appeal is still important, usability and effective interaction should be the top priority when developing a mobile app. A user wants to use their mobile app to save them time. From banking to shopping, there are mobile apps to serve the consumers’ needs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.computerweekly.com/feature/Making-mobile-apps-work&quot;&gt;Computer Weekly&lt;/a&gt;, A mobile app can help your company generate more income. If consumers can easily make a dinner reservation at a restaurant or purchase what they need, they are more likely to spend more money. Through the mobile app, you can also receive advertising income through in-app advertisements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mobile apps also help your company grow by users promoting your company. They can easily share products, reservations, tickets or specials via social media. The more users share content from the app, the more free publicity your company receives. You can also use push notifications to send upcoming specials directly to customers’ phones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Fobess, we can help you with your mobile needs. Our mobile technology group have great experience and many skills on different mobile technology innovations. When it comes to building mobile applications, we provide cross-platform mobile database integration. We’ll create a user-friendly program that serves your consumers’ needs. Contact us today to see how we can make the mobile application that’s perfect for you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Three things to keep in mind when developing mobile websites and apps</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/three-things-keep-mind-when-developing-mobile-websites-and-apps</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/three-things-keep-mind-when-developing-mobile-websites-and-apps</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 13:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;It’s not uncommon to look up in a room or on the street and see dozens of people glued to their phones. People are using the internet, surfing social media and even shopping and banking while mobile—and it’s essential that companies are able to meet needs on cell phones and tablets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what do you need to keep in mind when you take your business mobile?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Providing information to consumers is the top priority in developing a mobile application and website. A customer won’t take the time to learn about the services your company offers if the information isn’t readily available. Creating a clear navigation bar on a mobile website and a search engine can help your customers find the answers they need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saving time is a big goal when creating a mobile website and application. A mobile responsive site is important in keeping your audience’s attention, as they don’t want a clutter of information. A clean, organized website and mobile app is the best way to give your customers the answers they need in a short period of time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, entertainment is extremely important when creating a mobile application or website for gaming. After a long day at work, games are a go-to stress reliever for many individuals. Having a website that can support your gaming idea is critical or it won’t satisfy the customer’s needs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Across Borders Management Consulting Group, we know how to provide your customers what they need in a single mobile website or application. Whether it’s a mobile friendly web portal, transformable e-commerce website or any gaming ideas, we’ll help your app or website perform quickly. Contact us at 352-720-3135 or visit our website here to see how we can customize a plan for you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Across Borders merges with Fobess to form powerful technology solutions company</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/across-borders-merges-fobess-form-powerful-technology-solutions-company</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/across-borders-merges-fobess-form-powerful-technology-solutions-company</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 13:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Across Borders Management Consulting Group, a global technology solutions provider, has merged with Fobess, its sister company, in a move designed to promote growth and better serve clients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the move, Fobess will become Across Borders’ product division. The new company structure will make it easier for clients to shift between the two divisions to customize solutions to fit their needs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The newly combined company will offer all of the same services, and the same management team will oversee it. The company also looks to add positions as it continues to grow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We’ve seen the incredible demand from clients for the services both Across Borders and Fobess provide,” said Arathi Rajagopalan, Managing Partner. “This merger will make it easier for clients to find the exact solution they need, and it opens us up to continue to build on the success we’ve had in the past.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Across Borders creates a competitive advantage for organizations with customized, end-to-end IT solutions that leverage IBM, Microsoft and open source technologies. The company has expertise in the finance and mortgage, health care and retail fields. Fobess offers the latest domain-specific software and tools that allow businesses to hit the ground running. Products make it easy to launch everything from food delivery businesses and custom T-shirt design to job websites and crowdfunding capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Across Borders has received numerous recognitions for its growth. It was named to the Inc. 5,000 list in 2015 and 2016 and was named to the Orlando Business Journal’s Fast 50 in 2016. It has also been named to the GrowFL Florida Companies to Watch list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information about Across Borders, visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.integrass.com&quot;&gt;www.integrass.com.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Across Borders Management Consulting Group LLC Dba Integrass&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Across Borders Management Consulting Group LLC Dba Integrass is a global technology solutions provider that offers clients both customized, end-to-end IT solutions and products that are ready to launch through its product division, Fobess. Across Borders has expertise in the finance and mortgage, health care and retail fields. Its products make it easy to launch everything from food delivery businesses and custom T-shirt design to job websites. The company, which began operations in 2011, is woman and minority owned and based in Mount Dora, Fla. Across Borders has been honored numerous times for its outstanding growth. It has been named to the Inc. 5,000 list twice and made the Orlando Business Journal’s Fast 50 in 2016. It has also been named among Florida Companies to Watch by GrowFL. For more information, call (352) 720-3135 or visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.integrass.com&quot;&gt;www.integrass.com.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Technology is growing in education—and it’s important to keep up</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/technology-growing-educationand-its-important-keep</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/technology-growing-educationand-its-important-keep</guid>
			<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 13:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;As the world as a whole becomes more connected, it makes sense that education does, too. Students are already familiar with technology in their everyday lives, so bringing it into the classroom allows teachers and students both to do more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to a recent Babson Survey Research Group study, 28 percent of students now take at least one online course in their education, and this number is projected to grow. With this in mind, schools of all sizes and levels are evolving from hefty textbooks to laptops and tablets—and that can mean big benefits for students.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Digital practice quizzes and online homework assignments allow students to go at their own pace and understand their strengths and weaknesses. Assignments on a tablet or laptop can provide students the flexibility to learn the material when it works for their busy schedules.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And there are other lasting benefits. With the use of portable devices, students become familiar with common programs, such as Microsoft Office, and may dive deeper into more challenging undertakings, such as coding and design programs. Learning how to use various applications and programs allows students to set themselves up for future success in the workplace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But though bringing technology into the classroom can mean big benefits for students and teachers, it can be a challenging undertaking. The evolution of technology in education requires a platform with strong security controls, innovative strategies and streamlined communications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Across Borders Management Consulting Group, we have the experience in building student and teacher portals that better serve needs. Using the latest technology and innovative strategies, we can create a responsive software program that will adapt to changes in the industry. Learn more about our public sector IT solutions here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Veterans can receive free IT training, courtesy of Across Borders Management Consulting Group</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/veterans-can-receive-free-it-training-courtesy-across-borders-management-consulting-group</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/veterans-can-receive-free-it-training-courtesy-across-borders-management-consulting-group</guid>
			<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 13:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;After serving in the military, it can be difficult for veterans to readjust to civilian life. From relearning how to maintain a household to posttraumatic stress disorder, military personnel may need help after they’ve come home from their deployment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;May holds two holidays honoring those who’ve served in the military, and it is Military Appreciation Month. Armed Forces Day, which recognizes those who have and currently serve in the military, is the third Saturday of May. Memorial Day is observed the last Monday of May and gives the country the chance to mourn the soldiers who gave it all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Across Borders Management Consulting Group LLC Dba Integrass, we always honor military personnel with our Veteran Training Program. The program helps veterans by providing resources to those hoping to find a career in IT. After returning from service, they may lack what’s needed to gain knowledge in a specific field. Liberty Institution, a division of ABMCG, offers both training and career opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For all honorably discharged veterans, ABMCG waives the online tuition fees for Liberty Educate and testing fees for Liberty Certs. Workshops and career counseling are also available for Purple Heart recipients. Liberty Educate offers beginner to advanced training courses online to help veterans of all skill levels. Those just starting in software can take testing and introductory business courses, while experienced veterans can take advanced course curriculum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once retired military personnel are done with their training, they can find their next job on our Career Portal. This portal helps veterans translate military skills, build resumes, plan their transition and apply for career opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For veterans to begin their IT journey, contact ABMCG through the online form here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.abmcg.com/training/libertyinstitution&quot;&gt;http://www.abmcg.com/training/libertyinstitution&lt;/a&gt;. More information on Liberty Educate can be found here and information on Liberty Certs is located here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Do You Clear The Clutter in 2017 &amp; Go Open Source?</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/do-you-clear-clutter-2017-go-open-source</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/do-you-clear-clutter-2017-go-open-source</guid>
			<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 13:29:29 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;No matter what industry your business is in there is always room for improvement and the opportunity for change. Most people cringe when they hear the word technology used in a sentence with the word “change.” It’s the inevitable, with technology comes change! Our team at Fobess is excited for the new year to educate our clients about using an open source technology approach in their IT infrastructure. There are dozens of benefits to using this approach including cost reduction and increased productivity. The beauty of going to an open source technology platform gives us the opportunity to offer customizable solutions at a fraction of the price when compared to propriety software applications that may or may not be any better in functionality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An open source environment allows us to offer state of the art solutions. Those “tech gurus” working in an open software development environment are typically the best of the best, meaning these folks have spent countless hours and have an impressive resume to support their expertise in software development. What makes Fobess different from other open source consultants is our technical support. While some overlook the benefits of working in this type of environment due to the lack of support, our team at Fobess does quite the opposite…we thrive! Our consultants continue to work with clients beyond the installation and training for any open source solution we provide. Our technical support team offers round the clock support and we take full responsibility should our clients find flaws with the solutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlike proprietary solutions using an open source option can be much more customizable. Often a solution is built by developers who have a “one size fits all” mentality. Reality is “cookie cutter” applications do not work well across all industries. For example, in the healthcare industry HIPPA laws make it so providers must jump through several hoops in their data use and collection. An “off the shelf” solution may not take into account patient privacy laws. The financial industry is also highly regulated. Banks, financial advisors and even CPA’s must follow certain guidelines when shielding financial information of their clients. An open source option may offer such capabilities to keep financial institutions in compliance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Fobess we specialize in the following industries: healthcare, financial, banking, insurance, telecommunications, not-for-profit, and technology. Our developers are sensitive to the needs of highly regulated industries such as healthcare and financial. We encourage businesses to consider an open source application that can offer customization and better efficiencies compared to a “one size fits all” type of solution. Additionally, the expense can be astronomical with some of these proprietary models in the marketplace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are looking to make changes in 2017, and find a solution that is affordable and does everything to make your business more productive we invite you to call our team at Fobess. We offer free consultations, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.integrass.com/contact&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;contact us today!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Call us at 352-720-3164 and let our team help you discover the best open source technology opportunities available!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Cybersecurity: Protect your company’s assets and customers’ information</title>
			<link>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/cybersecurity-protect-your-companys-assets-and-customers-information</link>
			<guid>blog.integrass.com/blog/post/cybersecurity-protect-your-companys-assets-and-customers-information</guid>
			<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 12:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;When it comes to protecting your company’s assets, one of the biggest security measures that’s overlooked is cybersecurity. Companies are turning to their computers to digitally store their information, which takes up less physical storage spaces and makes it easier to find information. With more of your company’s information being stored digitally, cybersecurity is vital in securing your data and company information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.welivesecurity.com/2016/12/30/biggest-security-incidents-2016/&quot;&gt;We Live Security&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, there were some major cyberattacks in 2016. A major breach occurred for Tesco Bank when 60,000 bank accounts were compromised and thousands of people had as much as $763 drawn from their account. Another cyberattack happened to Yahoo this past year. Up to 50 million customers had their data stolen, including their phone numbers, emails, names and passwords. Not only are these cyberattacks bad for the company, but &lt;strong&gt;e-Channel &lt;a href=&quot;http://e-channelnews.com/storydetail.php?ref=410204&amp;amp;title=Gartner-Survey-Shows-Increased-Cyber-Attacks-Damage-Consumer-Trust-in-Online-Commerce&quot;&gt;News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; also says they damage consumers’ trust in the company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s important for your company to have a plan of action in case your company is unfortunate to get affected by a cyberattack. It’s important to take preventative measures, such as encrypting your data, securing your hardware and provide employee training. If your employees know how to spot potential breaches, you can stop a possible cyberattack before any damage is done. Firewalls and anti-virus programs can also help look out for possible threats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Figure out how your company will respond to a digital crisis. Be proactive and develop a plan early so you don’t have to make one after an attack has happened. Just like fire drills happen regularly, you should regularly rehearse cybersecurity action plans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Across Borders Management Consulting Group, we deliver security controls that deliver predictive analytics, prioritized threat data and real-time monitoring. Contact us today to see how we can optimize a plan for your company and its needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
